fascinate: v.   迷住，吸引住, affectionate: adj. 充满深情，柔情的
Lesson 9. Flying cats. Cats never fail to fascinate human beings. They can be friendly and affectionate towards humans.
第9课。飞猫。猫永远不会让人着迷。他们可以对人类友好和亲切。
mysterious: adj. 神秘的，难以理解的, submissive: adj. 服从的，顺从的
But they lead mysterious lives of their own as well. They never become submissive like dogs and horses.
但是他们也过着自己的神秘生活。他们永远不会像狗和马一样顺从。
feline: adj. 猫的, independence: n.   独立，独立性
As a result, humans have learned to respect feline independence. Most cats remain suspicious of humans all their lives.
结果，人类已经学会了尊重猫科动物的独立性。大多数猫一生都对人类保持怀疑。
fascinate: v.   迷住，吸引住
One of the things that fascinates us most about cats is the popular belief that they have nine lives.
我们对猫最吸引我们的一件事是普遍认为他们有九种生命。
Apparently, there is a good deal of truth in this idea. A cat's ability to survive falls is based on fact.
显然，这个想法有很多真相。猫生存的能力是基于事实。
Recently the New York Animal Medical Center made a study of 132 cats over a period of five months.
最近，纽约动物医疗中心在五个月的时间内研究了132只猫。
All these cats had one experience in common. They had fallen off high buildings.
所有这些猫都有共同的经验。他们从高建筑物上掉下来。
Yet only eight of them died from shock or injuries. Of course, New York is the ideal place for such an
然而，其中只有八人因冲击或受伤而丧生。当然，纽约是这样的理想场所
high-rise: adj. 高层的
interesting study. Because there is no shortage of tall buildings. There are plenty of high-rise
有趣的研究。因为不乏高大的建筑物。有很多高层
window-sills to fall from. One cat, Sabrina, fell 32 stories. Yet only suffered from a broken tooth.
窗台掉落。一只猫，萨布丽娜（Sabrina）摔倒了32层。然而，只有牙齿骨折。
paratrooper: n.   伞兵
Cats behave like well-trained paratroopers. A doctor said, it seems that the further cats fall.
猫的行为就像训练有素的伞兵。一位医生说，看来猫进一步倒下了。
The less they are likely to injure themselves. In a long drop, they reach speeds of 60 miles an hour
他们伤害自己的可能性就越少。长期下降，它们达到每小时60英里的速度
squirrel: n.   松鼠
and more. At high speeds, falling cats have time to relax. They stretch out their legs like flying squirrels.
还有更多。在高速的情况下，掉落的猫有时间放松。他们像飞翔的松鼠一样伸展腿。
impact: n.   冲击力
This increases their air resistance and reduces the shock of impact when they hit the ground.
这增加了他们的空气阻力，并减少了撞击地面时的冲击冲击。